

Senior Developer girish@gopaul.me +230 59010577

Mahébourg, Mauritius

# Girish Gopaul

#### **Profile**

Introduced to computer programming at the age of 14 by my father, I instantly fell in love with software development. I grew into becoming an extremely passionate and versatile developer with code quality as a core value. I am always excited to learn new frameworks and programming languages. Challenging tasks gets me pumped all the time. I have now been working professionally for 5+ years and my two favorite go-to framework are **Ruby on Rails** and **React**.

### **Employment History**

#### Consultant at Spoon Consulting, Mauritius

07/2017-09/2020

At Spoon Consulting I was immediately assigned to work with **Ruby on Rails** and **Angularjs** as **full-stack** developer. I have also worked with other various technologies such as developing **NPM** modules for **Nodejs** and **AWS Serverless**.

#### Software Developer at Elca, Ebene, Mauritius

09/2020-10/2021

At Elca, I was given the role of Front-End developer, I worked mostly with **Angular** and **React**.

# Senior Software Developer at Contractbook, Copenhagen

10/2021—Present

I am a full-stack developer at Contractbook and I work with **React** and **Elixir's Phoenix** (similar to **Rails**). Apart from feature development, I enjoy doing a lot of refactor from old class components to newer **functional components** in **typescript**. I also love doing SQL queries neatly using Phoenix's **Ecto**.

#### **Education**

**BSc (Hons) Computer Science, University of Mauritius** 

08/2014-07/2017

#### Skills

React & Redux	5/5
Ruby on Rails	5/5
JavaScript & TypeScript	5/5
Nodejs & Expressjs	5/5
Git	5/5
Elixir's Phoenix	5/5
Angular	4/5
Python & Django	4/5
Java	4/5
Flutter	4/5
PHP	4/5
C++	4/5
Linux	4/5
Redis	4/5
Vue.js & Svelte	3/5
NGINX Server	3/5

## **Certifications**

**Cisco Certified Network Associate** 

**Oracle Certified Java Associate** 

**Zend Certified Engineer 2017-PHP** 

#### Links

LinkedIn

# Languages

English	C2
French	C1